Wisdom Ighofose

7, Araba Street, Mosan, Lagos. +234(0)8164940763 wisdom.ighofose@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Exceptionally creative and dependable Web Developer with a stellar record and superb work ethic. Broadly and deeply knowledgeable in a wide variety of computer languages, frameworks and library as well as the principles and techniques of website construction and maintenance.

Core Skills and Qualifications

- Outstanding knowledge of web programming languages including PHP, CSS, HTML, JavaScript
- Exceptional organization and presentation abilities
- Excellent Knowledge and experienced WordPress and Woo-commerce integration
- Profound creative and analytical problem-solving and troubleshooting skills
- High verbal and written communication skills

Websites and Social links

Recent Projects

LinkedIn: linkedIn: linkedin.com/in/wisdom-ighofose-875424128/

GitHub: https://github.com/Wissy47

Freelancer: https://www.freelancer.com/u/blackrockwise

Pet Vet ID Processing: https://vetcareid.com
Web Development: https://cosmicare.com

Experience

Web Developer (Remote)

August, 2018 – Present CHRISHILL STUDIOS. AUSTRALIA https://chrishillstudios.com.au/about

- Writing efficient code for client websites such as www.vosa.org and www.weddingsbyvazmin.com.au
- Creating websites using standard HTML5/CSS3 practices
- Working closely with a team of web designers and programmers to produce bespoke websites such as www.vosa.org
- Constant communication with product designers, graphic designers, and other colleagues to review wireframes needed to develop and deploy their content – and ensure there is a clear establishment of what can be created within what timeframe.
- Implementing contingency plans in case the website goes down
- Maintaining and expanding/enhancing the website once built.

Business development manager

April, 2018 – 2021

OMAWIZ FARMS.

- Planning and overseeing new marketing initiatives.
- Researching organizations and individuals to find new opportunities.
- Increasing the value of current customers while attracting new ones.
- Finding and developing new markets and improving sales.
- Attending conferences, meetings, and industry events.
- Developing quotes and proposals for clients.
- Developing goals for the development team and business growth and ensuring they are met.

Fibre Optics Route Surveyor

December, 2019 -- March, 2020 (Contract) HUAWEI (IT SUPPORT)

- Fibre to the site survey
- Proposing possible route for fibre connection
- mapping of location where there is no fibre presence

Education

Bachelor's Degree – Counselling Psychology 2016 Delta State University

Certifications

Cambridge Certification Authority (CCA) - Web Development

Hobbies

Gaming, Reading, Traveling